Curriculum vitae Varje Kass

Contacts:

Address: Tiigi 13-9, Tartu 51003

Phone: 59 03 96 97

E-mail: varjekass@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/varje-kass

Web-page: http://varjekass.com

Introduction:

I am studying software development at Tartu Vocational Education Centre and I am a UI developer at STACC (Software Technology and Applications Competence Centre). My aim is to widen my expertise and gain experience as a programmer. I have experience with creating web-pages, web-applications and e-shops.

Education:

2016-present: vocational education: Tartu Vocational Education Centre, junior software

developer (web specialist)

2012-2016: higher education: University of Tartu, biology (bachelor's degree)

2008-2011: secondary education: Tartu Descartes Lyceum 1999-2008: basic education: Luunja Secondary School

Work experience:

Period	Company	Position
04.2017-present	STACC	UI developer
03.2016-04.2017	Baltmi AS	Encoder
10.2013-05.2016	University of Tartu	Microbiology internship
09.2011-02.2012	Coffee In	Barista
2007-2015, summers	Lemmatu Marjatalu	Berry picking, selling, packaging

Languages

Estonian – C2 English – C1 French – B1 Russian – A2

Computer skills

Python HTML5 CSS JavaScript PHP MySQL Photoshop

References

1.0.0.0.000		
Name	Company	Contact
Rena Piiroja,	Coffee IN	renapiiroja@gmail.com;
senior barista		55949410
Jana Bruns,	Baltmi AS	jana.bruns@baltmi.com;
project manager		53307823